Thank you, Lord
Severin, for accepting me.
From this moment on,
you are the new
head of the Morellan family.
Come on.
Let me escort my
bride to her throne.
Yes, my lord.
Listen, everyone.
Elowen Morellan, heir
of the Morellan family,
is the true
bride of this wedding.
She is my wife.
- Severin!
Hell yeah!
If you want to
be a kept man,
get the hell out
of the Holy Cathedral!
This is my wedding with Redmond.
Your wedding with Redmond?
Of course it is.
Did you forget I
publicly ended our engagement?
Redmond is my groom now.
Livia, you’ve even forgotten
who reserved this cathedral.
So what if you booked it?
The Scott family can
pay ten times the deposit.
Today I will marry Redmond here.
Take your woman and
get out of my cathedral!
to speak to my husband's family and wipe
that disgusting look off your face
You dared hit me?
Say one more word
and I can erase
your entire house
with a single command.